<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Yinan Zhao</title>
    <link>/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Yinan Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:57:28 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nestle CEO Campaign Competition</title>
      <link>/posts/nestle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/nestle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nestle, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading food and beverage company, has a wide range of product lines, from coffee to pet food. However, consumers have a limited understanding of Nestle&amp;rsquo;s entire product line, especially focusing on a few products such as coffee. This project aims to enhance consumers&amp;rsquo; awareness of Nestle products in various categories through virtual reality technology, as well as increase their interest and activity in purchasing across categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will launch a virtual reality experience called &amp;lsquo;Nestle World&amp;rsquo;. In the early stage of the project, we will let consumers experience in the form of pop-up stores. Within the virtual space, consumers will gain a deeper understanding of Nestle&amp;rsquo;s diverse products through an immersive and interactive experience. The experience will revolve around different virtual environments, such as a virtual kitchen, a virtual cafe and a virtual petting park, each of which will naturally fit into Nestle&amp;rsquo;s different product categories.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANKI memory card</title>
      <link>/posts/anki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/anki/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ANKI memory card is a powerful learning tool. It reifies the memorizing process and let users enjoy fun while memorizing. Its biggest feature is that it is highly personalized, and users can adjust the learning content and mode according to their learning habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this project, we designed a membership-based model for the further development of ANKI memory card. We analyzed competitor data and target demographics to design a solution that would marry business goals with consumer needs. In the process, we flexibly use 4PS, STP and other methods to improve our scheme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
