<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yinan Zhao</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yinan Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:57:28 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The main capital flow calculation of the stock market</title>
      <link>/posts/stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/stock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the stock market, the major capital refers to a trader who has concentrated a large amount of money and has the ability to lead the rise and fall of a stock. Therefore, it is important to identify the major capital in the stock market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project aims to output the main net inflow, main inflow, main outflow and individual volume and turnover of each time interval divided by T-window in the continuous bidding and closing aggregate bidding stages according to the given stock code and T-window.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haidilao Simulation Project</title>
      <link>/posts/haidilao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/haidilao/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a project that uses simulation to digitize real-world problems and provide solutions or improvements. We collect real-world data and use AnyLogic for system simulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Specifically, we use the queuing number collection online system of the Haidilao to collect number collection and number calling data for three consecutive days for subsequent arrival rate and service rate. We also went to a Haidilao to ask the staff about the store, including the floor area, the number of different table types and other information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Video Popularity Analysis</title>
      <link>/posts/youtubevideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/youtubevideo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a project that used Stata to analyze videos on YouTube trend. There are datasets of YouTube trend videos from 10 countries, including channel name, channel id, video id, video type, number of likes, number of dislikes, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I selected the data of South Korea to study what factors influenced the popularity of these videos, so that they could occupy a position in trend. I put forward four hypotheses as below:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nestle CEO Campaign Competition</title>
      <link>/posts/nestle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/nestle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nestle, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading food and beverage company, has a wide range of product lines, from coffee to pet food. However, consumers have a limited understanding of Nestle&amp;rsquo;s entire product line, especially focusing on a few products such as coffee. This project aims to enhance consumers&amp;rsquo; awareness of Nestle products in various categories through virtual reality technology, as well as increase their interest and activity in purchasing across categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will launch a virtual reality experience called &amp;lsquo;Nestle World&amp;rsquo;. In the early stage of the project, we will let consumers experience in the form of pop-up stores. Within the virtual space, consumers will gain a deeper understanding of Nestle&amp;rsquo;s diverse products through an immersive and interactive experience. The experience will revolve around different virtual environments, such as a virtual kitchen, a virtual cafe and a virtual petting park, each of which will naturally fit into Nestle&amp;rsquo;s different product categories.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album Management System</title>
      <link>/posts/albumsystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/albumsystem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When people buy albums, the logistics system is often a part of the attention of many people. When people are considering buying from different platforms, their choices often depend on the availability of stock, the speed of delivery, the timeliness of delivery, the accuracy of customer information, and the accuracy of sales. However, there are many problems in the logistics system of many platforms nowadays, such as insufficient stock, album misdistribution, missing distribution, and sales reflection is not timely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANKI memory card</title>
      <link>/posts/anki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/anki/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ANKI memory card is a powerful learning tool. It reifies the memorizing process and let users enjoy fun while memorizing. Its biggest feature is that it is highly personalized, and users can adjust the learning content and mode according to their learning habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this project, we designed a membership-based model for the further development of ANKI memory card. We analyzed competitor data and target demographics to design a solution that would marry business goals with consumer needs. In the process, we flexibly use 4PS, STP and other methods to improve our scheme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implement chess interface in Java</title>
      <link>/posts/javaproj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:57:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/javaproj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project aims to complete the front end chess interface, and implements the back end logic according to chess rules in Java. Our program, when run, allows two people to play a normal chess match, with countdown reminders and reminder routes for both sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1j6a4w2IaC70O7rWcCvJKahxSX3hgz6Tj?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Code and report for chess implement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
